UCLA University Archives. Moving image and audio recordings. ca.1940- UARC.0642
UCLA Library Special Collections
UCLA University Archives. Moving image and audio recordings.
ca.1940-
UCLA Library Special Collections
UARC.0642
999 linear feet
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 642 contains miscellaneous moving image and audio recordings of UCLA events and activities, including: UCLA Charter Day lectures; UCLA Convocations; UCLA Faculty Lecture Series; the UCLA Committee on Public Lectures; UCLA Friend of the Library events; and moving image footage by Stan Troutman, c.1930-1970.
Related Material
SEE ALSO: Record Series 333 Public Information Office. Moving image and audio recordings.
- Page Ackerman - Birthday Party., 1958 May 07.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
  General note
  sound only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 01, jej
- Charter Day - system wide at Berkeley, John Fitzgerald Kennedy, speaker., 1962 Mar 23.; 7in. audio tape. (Box 1)
  sound only, contents confirmed 2013 Feb 28, jej
- Walter Starkie - Theater of the Absurd: from Pirandello to Beckett., 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
  sound only, not in box 2013 Mar 28 jej
- Robert Stevenson - "Calderonian Opera", commemoraating tercentenary of Pedro Calderon del la Barca, includes program., 1981 Apr 16.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Memorial Service- Regent Edward A. Dickson, speakers include Robert Sproul, Edwin Pauley, Vern Knudsen, Lawrence Clark Powell, M. Philip Davis, Raymond Allen,., 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Memorial Service- Ernest Carroll Moore, speakers include Ramond B. Allen, Thomas J. Conningham, Edwin A. Lee, Lawrence Clark Powell, Robert Gordon Sproul., 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
  sound only, contents confirmed 2013 Feb 28, jej, tape Marked copy
- Football - Red Sanders Day, Grantland Rice Award and Football Banquet- speakers include Wilbur Johns, Rube Samuelson, Tim Cohane, Dan Mich., 1954 Dec 10.; 7 in. audio tape, 5 tapes. (Box 1)
- Demonstration Interview with Emmet Lavery by Elizabeth Dixon, symposium of UCLA Library, LA Federal Records Center, Society Of American Archivists., 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Crowning Queen, Rose Bowl, Sanders, yells, rallies, pregame and postgame., 1954, 1955, 1956, 1957.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Convocation Address - Luther Evans, to the UCLA School of Library Service., 1961 Sep 27.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Walter Starkie - Historical Survey of the Gypsies., 7 in. audio tape. (Box 1)
- Chancellor Charles E. Young - Town Hall., 1969 Apr 29.; 7 in. audio tape, 2 tapes. (Box 2)
  2 tapes of 2, audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 01 jej
- Lecture - Ralph Ellison, "The Novelist and His Form," Royce Hall., 1964 Apr 07-08.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  2 tapes of 2, tapes Marked "dupe", audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar jej
- Robert Vosper - Retirement convocation, transcript of reMarks by Page Ackerman, Lawrence Clark Powell, Chancellor Franklin Murphy and Robert Shackleton., fair copy. (Box 2)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 20 jej
- Robert Vosper - Retirement convocation., 1973 Jun 08.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar jej
- President Clark Kerr and Regent Carter - Press Conference., 1964 Dec 18.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  3 tapes of 3, audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 01 jej
- Lecture - Ewing Lectures, Angus Wilson., 1960 Oct 24, 26 and 27.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
- J.A.C. Grant - History of University and William Carlos Williams., 1950 Nov 15.; 5 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  tape not in box 2013 Mar 01 jej
- Dedication - Young Research Library Department of Special Collections, address by Lawrence Clark Powell, Parts 1 and 2., 1951 (?).; 5 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  tapes not in box
- Chancellor Franklin D. Murphy - unidentified content., 7 in. audio tape, 2 tapes. (Box 2)
  Parts 1 and 2, audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 01 jej
- Chancellor Franklin D. Murphy--Personal Portrait., 1965 May 01-02.; 7 in. audio tape. (Box 2)
  1 tape, audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 01 jej
- Friends of the Library Fourth Annual Meeting., 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 3)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 015 jej
- Friends of theLibrary - Paul Jordan Smith, "The Pleasures and Perils of Book Collecting," speakers include Lawrence Clark Powell, Majl Ewing, Dwight Clark, Harold Lamb., 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 3)
- Memorial Service - Vern O. Knudsen, speakers include Charles Young, David Saxon, Victor Goodhill, Gustave Arlt, Franklin Murphy, Henri Temianka., 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 3)
- Friends of the Library - Paul Wellman, "How I Write an Historical Novel," speakers include Dwight Clark, Lawrence Clark Powell., 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 3)
- Walter Starkie - Notes on the Irish Theater, UCLA Extension course 1973., folder. (Box 3)
  not in box 2013 Mar 015 jej
- Friends of the Library - J. Frank Dobie, "Literature of the Southwest,"., 1954 Nov 30.; 7 in. magnetic tape, 4 tapes. (Box 3)
- Friends of the Library - First Meeting, "Anecdotes of Medical Californians," speakers include Stafford Warren, Lawrence Clark Powell, WW Robinson, John Saunders., 1954 Jun 10.; 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 3)
- Friends of the Library- Dedication of the One Millionth Volume, speakers include W.W. Robinson, Charles Camp, David Magee, Regent Dickson, Chancellor Allen, Lawrence Clark Powell, Lindley Bynum., 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 3)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Tom Schultz, Royce Hall., 1974 Jul 10.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 4)
- Schoenberg Hall Open House., 1963 Nov 17.; 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 4)
- UC Riverside - Dedication Ceremony., 1954 Oct 22.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 4)
- Library Acquisitions Round Table., 1953 Nov 23.; 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 4)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, speaker unidentified., 1974 Jul 17 and 24.; 7 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 4)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Ganett Hardin, Royce Hall., 1974 Jul 03.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 4)
- Friends of the Library - Tribute to Robert and Blanche Campbell., 1974 Jul 31.; 7 in. and 5 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 4)
- Biomedical Library - Opening Ceremony, speakers include Louise Darling, JoSeph Ross, Theodore Dunn, LC Powell., 1954 Oct 25.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 4)
- Library Staff Association - Party, Lawrence Clark Powell speaking on Millionth Volume, tribute to old staff members,., 1953 Nov 11.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 4)
  audio only,contents confirmed 2013 Mar 015 jej
- ASUCLA - Official Record Album, MilMark Collegiate Band, Herman McCoy Singers (Box 5)
  audio only; this album has been digitized: uars_642_005.001
- Lecture - Earth 2020, JoSeph Coates, Royce Hall, 1974 August 21; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 014 jej
- Lecture - Earth 2020, speaker not identified, 1974 July 31; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Royce Hall Master #8287 - Documentary voice-over with music, n.d.; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Richard Garner, Royce Hall, 1974 September 04; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Michael Arbib, Royce Hall, 1974 August 28; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, John McCall, Royce Hall, 1974 June 26; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Ian McHarg, Royce Hall, 1974 August 07; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Lecture - Earth 2020, Kenneth Boulding, Royce Hall, 1974 August 14; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Chancellor Franklin D. Murphy - talk on Proposition 1-A at NPI auditorium, introduced by Stafford Warren, 1962 October 30; magnetic tape. (Box 5)
- Clark Memorial Library - Chancellor Franklin Murphy Presentation to the Regents, 1962 April 26; magnetic tape, 3 tapes. (Box 5)
- D.H. Lawrence Roundtable - Speakers include Lawrence Clark Powell, Majl Ewing, Grover Jacoby, Aldous Huxley, Frieda Lawrence and Mrs. D. Mitchell, 1952 March 07; 7 in. magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 6)
  audio only, tape labeled: master in special collections. See box 139 for CD duplicate; contents confirmed 2013 Mar 21 jej
- UCLA Campus Footage, 1930s (Box 6)
- Lecture - Richard Neutra Memorial Inaugural Lecture, Rene Dubos, Rockefeller University, "Shelters, Open Spaces and Adaptations", no date; audio cassette, 2 cassettes. (Box 6)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 018 jej
- Faculty Lecture Series Winter 1980 - Mildred Mathias, "Reserves for the Future Preservation of Natural, 1980 January 23; audio cassette. (Box 6)
- Faculty Lecture Series Winter 1980 - Dean Robert Hayes, "The Information Age-Its Implications for Research", 1980 winter; audio cassette, 2 cassettes. (Box 6)
- Faculty Lecture Series Winter 1980 - David Rodes, "Deep Play in Private Houses-the Gamble for Love in Restoration Comedy", 1980 February 06; audio cassette. (Box 6)
- Oral History Institute: Page Ackerman; Edna C. Davis; L. Mathies; Paul Miles; Nevins and Shruben, 1968 July; 5 tapes; magnetic tape (Box 6)
- Carillion Recording- Alumni Anniversary, 1973 June 09; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 6)
- Faculty Lecture Series Winter 1980 - Christopher Salter, "O Say Can We See, A Geographer Looks at Landscape", 1980 January 30; audio cassette. (Box 6)
- Michael Straight, Deputy Chair, National Endowment for the Arts, speaking at Freud Playhouse, 1971 April 01; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 019 jej
- Lecture - University Committee on Public Lectures, Hans Kung, "The Church and Sincerity", 1966 November 03; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Lecture - Stanislav Grof, 1971 February 18; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Lecture - Richard Neutra Memorial Lecture - Robert Coles, Harvard University, "People and the American Land," Introduction, Dion Neutra, no date; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Spring 1972: The Family and the Future - Sandra Garcia, "Racism and the Role of the Male in the Black Family of the Future", 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Spring 1972: The Family and the Future - Roderic Gorney, "On Healthier Future Human Relationships: Interpersonal Intensity and Social Synergy", 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Spring 1972: The Family and the Future - Hy Faine, "Culture-Home Bound or Outward Bound?", 1972 May 15.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series - Spring 1972, Jerome Cohen, "Family Life Styles and the Counter Culture"., 1972 May 01.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Spring 1972: The Family and the Future - Ralph Turner, "The Conjugal Family-Has it a Future?", 1972 April 24; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Fall 1970: Bridging Two Worlds - Victoria Fromkin, "The Study of Linguistics as a Science and as a Humanity, 1970 November 09; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Fall 1970: Bridging Two Worlds - Philip Borden, "History as an Orgone Box-The Future of History as Science"., 1970 October 26; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Fall 1970: Bridging Two Worlds - James Krier, "Technology, Environmental Quality and Corporate Responsibility", 1970 November 02; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Fall 1970: Bridging Two Worlds - Vincent Dearing, "Why Johnny Computer Can't Read - Studying Literature with an Illiterate Computer", 1970 November; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Faculty Lecture Series Fall 1970: Bridging Two Worlds - Leon Knopoff, "From Bach to Bits: The Present and Future of Computer Music", 1970 November; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 7)
- Basketball - John Wooden Retirement Salute, 1975 October 14; 7 in. (Box 7)
  audio only, not in box 2013 Mar 019 jej
- Powell Flood - James V. Mink interviewed by Joel Gardner, 1975 August 07-08; 5 in. magnetic tape, two tapes. (Box 8)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 21 jej
- Starkie, W. #1, 1973 January 10 (Box 8)
- UCLA School of Medicine - Charles Huggins on Orchiectomy, introduced by Willard Gooodwin, 1962 February 21; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 8)
- Friends of the Library - unidentfied topic, speakers include Robert Vosper, Franklin Murphy, Betty Rosenberg, (Loren?) Rothschild, no date; 5 in. magnetic tape, two tapes. (Box 8)
- Friends of the Library - Joel Gardner, "Interviewing Carey McWilliams" other speakers include Blake Nevins and John Weaver., 1979 Dec 12.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 8)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 20 jej
- Copyright Seminar., 1973 May 04.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 8)
  labeled Tape I, audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 21 jej
- History of UCLA on Oral History Meeting., 1977 Nov 22.; 5 in. (Box 8)
- Nomad Conference (?) - speakers include Bulliet, Fahim, Prussin, Altman, Behnke, Watson, Segall and Weisner., 5 in. magnetic tape,four tapes. (Box 9)
- University History - Oral History Program Demonstration Tape, speakers include Bennett Allen, Hale Sparks, Stafford Warren, Lawrence Clark Powell, Hansena Frederickson, Flora Scott, Vern Knudsen, Franklin Murphy and Adaline Guenther., 1971.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- UCLA Librarian - Interview with Ruth Gibbs and Dan Tonkery., 1980 Jan 16.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Carey McWilliams Graduate Fellowship and Undergraduate Honors Awards - First anniversary reception., 1983 Feb 14.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
  audio only; recorded by Dale Trelevan; contents confirmed 2013 Mar 018 jej
- Phi Delta Kappa Symposium - Current Issues and Concern in Public Education, Donald E. Wilson and William Fitzpatric., 1967 Feb 03.; 5 in., magnetic tape, 3 tapes. (Box 9)
- Memorial - Elmer Belt, speakers include Robert Vosper, Stafford Warren, Willard Goodwin, Carlo Pedretti, Jake Zeitlin, and Lynn White, Jr., 1980 Jan 14.; 5 in., one tape. (Box 9)
- Lecture - Paul Hockings, UCLA Anthropological Association., 1968 Nov 14.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Friends of the Library - unidentified speaker., 1975 Oct 12.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Friends of the Library - Robert Nathan, "One More Spring" speakers include Blake Nevins, John Weaver, Russell Shank, Jack Smith., 1979 Mar 21.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Friends of the Library - Lynn White featured speaker, unidentified topic, speakers include Louise Darling, John Weaver and Russell Shank., 5" magnetic tpae. (Box 9)
  audio only, not in box 2013 Mar 015 jej
- Friends of the Library - Helen Wallace, "Nova Albion," speakers include Russell Shank, Norman Thomas and John CAughey., 1979 Jul 25.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Friends of the Library - "A Diamond for Jake [Zeitlin]" tribute, speakers include Russell Shank, John Weaver and Lynn White., 1977 Nov 04.; 5 in., magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 9)
- Friends of the Library - Upton Sinclair and EPIC, speakers include Russell Shank, John Weaver, Philip Dunne, Aaron Gottesman and Jerry Voorhis., 1978 Nov 29.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 9)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 018
- UCLA Emeriti Association - Philip E. Chandler, "The Evolution of UCLA's Landscape Environment, 1933 to the Present"., 1975 Nov 13.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 9)
- Charter Day - Admiral Chester William Nimitz., 1950 Mar 23.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- UCLA Affiliates - Tribute to Jules and Doris Stein - Speakers include Drs. Stafford Warren, Eliot Corday, Sherman Mellinkoff, Bradley Straatsma, and Chancellor Charles E. Young with responding reMarks by Dr. Stein., 1977 Mar 010.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
  includes ribbon copy and finished transcript of recording; tape is audio only; contents confirmed 2013 Mar 019 jej
- President Clark Kerr Dismissal - track one: Theodore Meyer, Chair, University of California Board of Regents press conference held after UC Regents meeting dismissing Clark Kerr; track two: reMarks by Dr. Kerr concerning the dismissal., 1967 Jan 20.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
  copied from a rough master; audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 019 jej
- Memorial - Clarence Dkystra., 1950 May 10.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- Memorial - Adaline C. Guenther, speakers include Gilbert A. Harrison and Mayor Tom Bradley., 1975 Oct 12.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
  includes official program of the service; audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 019 jej
- Martin Luther King Jr. - Memorial Service held at Royce Hall., 1968 Apr 08.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- Louise Chimes., 1969 Jul 26.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- Dedication - Young Research Library Department of Special Collections Rare Book Rooms, speakers include Majl Ewing, Henry Wagner, George Harding, John CAughey, James Babb and Lawrence Clark Powell., 1950 Jul 28.; 5 in. magnetic tape, 2 reels. (Box 10)
- Basketball Men - Awards Banquet., 1969 May 07.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- UCLA School of Library and Information Science - address by Lawrence Clark Powell., 1975 Jun 03.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
  audio only, copied from videotape; contents confirmed 2013 Mar 019 jej
- Eleanor Roosevelt - speech delivered at Royce Hall: The Responsibility of the United States to the United Nations., 1950 Jan 19.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- UCLA Graduate School of Journalism., 1950 Feb 13.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- UCLA Law School., n.d.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 10)
- Lecture - Advanced Endrocrinology-Receptor Theory., 1980 Apr 08.; Cassette. (Box 11)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- UCLANS in Song., 1957-58.; Cassettes. (Box 11)
  not in box 2013 Mar 25 jej
- UCLA - Day at UCLA Highlights, KABC., 1988 Feb 04.; Cassette. (Box 11)
- Our Year in Sound., 1956-57.; Cassettes. (Box 11)
- Lecture - UCLA Department of Philosophy, History of the Department., 1994 May 13.; 8 mm cassette, 2 tapes. (Box 11)
  Edited and confirmed 2007 Jan 5 (MLS).
- Lecture - Steroid Structure., 1980 Feb 15.; Cassette. (Box 11)
- Lecture - Albert Hoxie: "Hollywood in Its Heyday" introduced by David Clark., 1974 July 24.; Cassette. (Box 11)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- Go! Go!! Bruin Baby! - Don Davis., Cassette. (Box 11)
  audio only, content confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- Football - UCLA 20 vs USC 16, last 7 minutes of game, KTTV Bill Welsh announcing., 1965 Nov 20.; cassette. (Box 11)
- Football - Dick Vermeil, first press conference as head coach., 1974.; 1 CD-Audio. (Box 11)
  audio only, CD copy dated 2006 Nov 22, on same CD as John Wooden Louisville press conferences contents confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- Football - Dick Vermeil, first press conference as head coach., 1974.; cassette. (Box 11)
  audio only, on same cassette as John Wooden Louisville press conferences, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- Community Affairs and Development Committee Program CDAC - "Health Insurance What's Best For You"., 1983 Dec 08.; Cassette. (Box 11)
- Commencement., 1985.; cassette, 2 tapes. (Box 11)
- Basketball men - John Wooden News Conference before and after NCAA semifinal game against Louisville., 1975 March 29.; Cassette. (Box 11)
  Confirmed 2007 Jan 5 (MLS).
- Basketball men - John Wooden News Conference before and after NCAA Semifinal game against Louisville., 1975 March 29.; CD-R audio. (Box 11)
  audio only, CD copy dated 2006 Nov 22, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 25 jej
- Basketball men - John Wooden News Conference after winning 1975 NCAA West Regional Playoff vs Arizona State (ASU)., 1975 March 22.; Cassette. (Box 11)
- Lecture - Hormone action: undergraduate recording., 1980 Mar 05.; cassette. (Box 11)
- Francis Crick - Jacob Marschak Memorial Lecture, "The Problem of Visual Awareness and the Neural Basis of Consciousness"., 1994 Feb 18.; vhs. (Box 12)
  video, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 26 jej
- Is Freedom Academic? - KPFA radio documentary of the UC Berkeley Free Speech movement, narrator: Scott Keech., 1964 Fall.; 7 in. magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 12)
  audio only, audio available online at http://www.kpfahistory.info/pa/is_freedom_academic.mp3, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 26 jej
- Should Teachers Organize? - KCET broadcast, speakers include ? Brown, JoSeph Brooks, William Lambert, Hank Zivety, Jean Thompson and UCLA Dean Howard Wilson., 1965 July 30.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 12)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 26 jej
- Make It Happen: Student and Campus Life at UCLA., vhs. (Box 12)
- Lecture - Richard P. Feynman: "Photons: Particles of Light", tapes 1 and 2 of 2., 1983 May 03.; vhs, 2 tapes. (Box 12)
  video, contents confirmed 2013 Mar jej
- Lecture - Richard P. Feynman: "Fits of Reflection and Transmission: Quantum Behavior", tape 2 of 3., 1983 May 05.; vhs, 1 tape. (Box 12)
- Football - Beat 'SC Rally and Bonfire., 1994 Nov 17.; vhs. (Box 12)
- Commencement - UCLA, 42d annual commencement., 1961 Jun 10.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 12)
- Charter Day, 1964 - soundtrack of film [see box 29 for film]. Narration by Hale Sparks., 1964 Feb 21. (Box 12)
- Chancellor's Convocation., 1961 Sep 18.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 12)
- Afternoon Session (continued)., 1973 Jun 09.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 12)
  tape not in box, 2013 Mar 26 jej
- A Bruin Named Joe., 1953.; vhs. (Box 12)
- Lecture - Howard Eugene Wilson, Dean, School of Education, "Interchange of Persons"., 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 12)
- Charter Day - System wide, Charles Hitch speaker, held in Royce Hall., 1975 Apr 03.; 7 in. magnetic tape, 2 tapes. (Box 13)
- Ralph Bunche in Retrospect - Transcript of reMarks by Brian Urquhart at the First Exhibition of the Ralph Bunche Papers., 1975 Apr 15.; paper transcript. (Box 13)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 014 jej
- Ralph Bunche In Retrospect - Remarks by Brian Urquhart at the First Exhibition of the Ralph Bunche Papers., 1975 Apr 15.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Ralph Bunche in Retrospect - Opening Remarks by Page Ackerman at the First Exhibition of the Ralph Bunche Papers., 1975 Apr 14.; paper transcript. (Box 13)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 26 jej
- Lecture - Ralph Bunche, "The Challenges of Modern Africa", Fourth UCLA Social Science Research Lecture, Royce Hall., 1961 Apr 17.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Commencement - Program., 1962 Jun 08.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Charter Day - Luncheon., 1975 Apr 03.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Charter Day - George Beadle, speaker., 1962 Mar 27.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Chancellor Franklin P. Murphy - Press Conference #41., 1962 Oct 21.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Banquet - Drake., n.d.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Anglo-American Cataloging - 2nd Session., 1967 Apr 27.; 7 in. magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Lecture - Goodwin J. Knight, former governor of California, "What Price Liberty?", Royce Hall., 1963 May 08.; 7 in., magnetic tape. (Box 13)
- Friends of the Library - speakers include Jack Smith, Leonard Wibberly, Robert Nathan and John Weaver., 1977 Aug 24.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- School of Architecture, Dean's Forum, co-sponsored by the Atlantic Monthly - Los Angeles Comes of Age., 1988 Feb 05.; Master Cassette. (Box 14)
- School of Architecture, Dean's Council Dinner, Union Station - J. Irwin Miller., 1987 Apr 21.; Cassette. (Box 14)
- School of Architecture, Dean's Council Dinner - Max De Pree., 1983.; Cassette. (Box 14)
- School of Architecture, Dean's Council Dinner, Greystoke (?) - I M Pei., 1988 Jun 14.; Cassette. (Box 14)
- School of Architecture Preservation Conference, Wiltern Theatre., 1981 Nov 02; 1981 Dec 02.; Cassette, 2 cassettes. (Box 14)
- UCLA Alumni and Development Center - 55th Anniversary of UCLA, held at Dickson Art Center., 1974 Jun 01.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 14)
  audio only, contents confirmed 2013 Mar 014
- KBIG Salutes to UCLA., n.d.; 5" magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- Friends of the Library - Carl Foreman, guest speaker, with Henry Goodman and John Weaver., 1976 Aug 04.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- Friends of the Library - Jack Smith, featured speaker, with John Weaver, Gladwin Hill, Neal Morgan and H. Ward Ritchie., 1973 Apr 25.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 14)